exploremodeling.com 2012-09-15

# Explore Modeling - Our Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our web site. Explore Modeling is committed to providing a safe and secure environment for all of its site members. Protecting your online privacy is a part of that committment. 

This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

 **Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, phone numbers, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our members. The information you provide is used to fulfill you specific requests and needs with respect to your activites on the website. For example, we may need to contact you by phone for a specific casting opportunity, or, we may need your postal address to mail your composite cards. This information is only used to fulfill your specific requests and needs on the site. From time to time, you may have the opportunity to receive additional information from one our partner websites, but this is stricly optional.

 **Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties, but this information will not contain your personal information.

 **Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. 

**Questions?**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the "Contact Us" link at the bottom of our site.

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

last update: 9/29/2010
